(function(){const e=document.createElement("link").relList;if(e&&e.supports&&e.supports("modulepreload"))return;for(const t of document.querySelectorAll('link[rel="modulepreload"]'))h(t);new MutationObserver(t=>{for(const n of t)if(n.type==="childList")for(const l of n.addedNodes)l.tagName==="LINK"&&l.rel==="modulepreload"&&h(l)}).observe(document,{childList:!0,subtree:!0});function i(t){const n={};return t.integrity&&(n.integrity=t.integrity),t.referrerpolicy&&(n.referrerPolicy=t.referrerpolicy),t.crossorigin==="use-credentials"?n.credentials="include":t.crossorigin==="anonymous"?n.credentials="omit":n.credentials="same-origin",n}function h(t){if(t.ep)return;t.ep=!0;const n=i(t);fetch(t.href,n)}})();document.getElementById("coding");document.getElementById("music");document.getElementById("moderart");let g=document.getElementById("question");document.getElementsByClassName("choice-text");let p=document.getElementById("option1"),f=document.getElementById("option2"),y=document.getElementById("option3"),w=document.getElementById("option4");document.getElementById("nextQuestion");let q=document.getElementById("save"),m={music:[{id:1,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",options:["Standard notation","Tab notation","Morse code notation","Graphics notation"],answer:"Morse code notation",category:"music"},{id:2,question:"What is the most common time signature in classical music?",options:["3/4","4/4","5/4","6/8"],answer:"4/4",category:"music"},{id:3,question:"Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",options:["Violin","Piano","Harp","Theremin"],answer:"Theremin",category:"music"},{id:4,question:"What is the most common key in pop music?",options:["C Major","G Major","D Major","A Major"],answer:"C Major",category:"music"},{id:5,question:"Which of the following is not a type of chord?",options:["Major","Minor","Diminished","Flat"],answer:"Flat",category:"music"},{id:6,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",options:["Jazz","Blues","Rock","Applesauce"],answer:"Applesauce",category:"music"},{id:7,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",options:["Harmony","Counterpoint","Form","Cooking"],answer:"Cooking",category:"music"},{id:8,question:"What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",options:["Allegro","Andante","Adagio","Moderato"],answer:"Allegro",category:"music"},{id:9,question:"Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",options:["Sonata","Symphony","Concerto","Spaghetti"],answer:"Spaghetti",category:"music"},{id:10,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",options:["Sibelius","Finale","MuseScore","Microsoft Word"],answer:"Microsoft Word",category:"music"}],"modern-art":[{id:11,question:"Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:12,question:"Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Futurism","Cubism"],answer:"Cubism",category:"modern-art"},{id:13,question:"Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:14,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",options:["Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Edvard Munch","Claude Monet"],answer:"Edvard Munch",category:"modern-art"},{id:15,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Fauvism","Cubism"],answer:"Fauvism",category:"modern-art"},{id:16,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",options:["Impressionism","Futurism","Surrealism","Abstract Expressionism"],answer:"Futurism",category:"modern-art"},{id:17,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",options:["Claude Monet","Paul Cezanne","Paul Gauguin","Paul Klee"],answer:"Claude Monet",category:"modern-art"},{id:18,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",options:["Henri Matisse","Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Pablo Picasso"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:19,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",options:["Claude Mone","Paul Cezanne","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:20,question:"Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",options:["Auguste Rodin","Alexander Calder","Jean Arp","Henry Moore"],answer:"Auguste Rodin",category:"modern-art"}],coding:[{id:21,question:"What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",options:["if (condition):","if condition","if: condition","if condition:"],answer:"if condition:",category:"coding"},{id:22,question:"Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",options:["String","Number","Boolean","ArrayList"],answer:"ArrayList",category:"coding"},{id:23,question:"Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",options:["var","let","const","int"],answer:"int",category:"coding"},{id:24,question:"What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",options:["for i = 0 to 10","for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)","for (int i = 0; i <= 10)","for i in range(0, 10)"],answer:"for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",category:"coding"},{id:25,question:"Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",options:["while","for","do-while","foreach"],answer:"foreach",category:"coding"},{id:26,question:"Which of the following is not a valid operator in C++?",options:["+","-","*","$"],answer:"$",category:"coding"},{id:27,question:"In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"Python",category:"coding"},{id:28,question:"What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",options:["function name()","def name","function name","def name()"],answer:"def name()",category:"coding"},{id:29,question:"Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",options:["Int","String","Double","Object"],answer:"Object",category:"coding"},{id:30,question:"In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"C++",category:"coding"}]},v=Array.from(m.coding.map(o=>o));Array.from(m.music.map(o=>o));Array.from(m["modern-art"].map(o=>o));let a={},c=[];startCodingGame=()=>{score=0,c=[...v],getNewQuestion()};getNewQuestion=()=>{let o=["","","",""];const e=Math.floor(Math.random()*c.length);a=c[e],g.innerText=a.question;for(let i=0;i<a.options.length;i++)o[i]=a.options[i];p.nextSibling.textContent=o[0],f.nextSibling.textContent=o[1],y.nextSibling.textContent=o[2],w.nextSibling.textContent=o[3],c.splice(e,1),q.addEventListener("click",()=>{})};startCodingGame();document.getElementById("music");let W=document.getElementById("question");document.getElementsByClassName("choice-text");let b=document.getElementById("option1"),M=document.getElementById("option2"),C=document.getElementById("option3"),S=document.getElementById("option4");document.getElementById("nextQuestion");let P={music:[{id:1,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",options:["Standard notation","Tab notation","Morse code notation","Graphics notation"],answer:"Morse code notation",category:"music"},{id:2,question:"What is the most common time signature in classical music?",options:["3/4","4/4","5/4","6/8"],answer:"4/4",category:"music"},{id:3,question:"Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",options:["Violin","Piano","Harp","Theremin"],answer:"Theremin",category:"music"},{id:4,question:"What is the most common key in pop music?",options:["C Major","G Major","D Major","A Major"],answer:"C Major",category:"music"},{id:5,question:"Which of the following is not a type of chord?",options:["Major","Minor","Diminished","Flat"],answer:"Flat",category:"music"},{id:6,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",options:["Jazz","Blues","Rock","Applesauce"],answer:"Applesauce",category:"music"},{id:7,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",options:["Harmony","Counterpoint","Form","Cooking"],answer:"Cooking",category:"music"},{id:8,question:"What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",options:["Allegro","Andante","Adagio","Moderato"],answer:"Allegro",category:"music"},{id:9,question:"Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",options:["Sonata","Symphony","Concerto","Spaghetti"],answer:"Spaghetti",category:"music"},{id:10,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",options:["Sibelius","Finale","MuseScore","Microsoft Word"],answer:"Microsoft Word",category:"music"}],"modern-art":[{id:11,question:"Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:12,question:"Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Futurism","Cubism"],answer:"Cubism",category:"modern-art"},{id:13,question:"Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:14,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",options:["Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Edvard Munch","Claude Monet"],answer:"Edvard Munch",category:"modern-art"},{id:15,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Fauvism","Cubism"],answer:"Fauvism",category:"modern-art"},{id:16,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",options:["Impressionism","Futurism","Surrealism","Abstract Expressionism"],answer:"Futurism",category:"modern-art"},{id:17,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",options:["Claude Monet","Paul Cezanne","Paul Gauguin","Paul Klee"],answer:"Claude Monet",category:"modern-art"},{id:18,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",options:["Henri Matisse","Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Pablo Picasso"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:19,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",options:["Claude Mone","Paul Cezanne","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:20,question:"Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",options:["Auguste Rodin","Alexander Calder","Jean Arp","Henry Moore"],answer:"Auguste Rodin",category:"modern-art"}],coding:[{id:21,question:"What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",options:["if (condition):","if condition","if: condition","if condition:"],answer:"if condition:",category:"coding"},{id:22,question:"Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",options:["String","Number","Boolean","ArrayList"],answer:"ArrayList",category:"coding"},{id:23,question:"Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",options:["var","let","const","int"],answer:"int",category:"coding"},{id:24,question:"What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",options:["for i = 0 to 10","for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)","for (int i = 0; i <= 10)","for i in range(0, 10)"],answer:"for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",category:"coding"},{id:25,question:"Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",options:["while","for","do-while","foreach"],answer:"foreach",category:"coding"},{id:26,question:"Which of the following is not a valid operator in C++?",options:["+","-","*","$"],answer:"$",category:"coding"},{id:27,question:"In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"Python",category:"coding"},{id:28,question:"What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",options:["function name()","def name","function name","def name()"],answer:"def name()",category:"coding"},{id:29,question:"Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",options:["Int","String","Double","Object"],answer:"Object",category:"coding"},{id:30,question:"In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"C++",category:"coding"}]},x=Array.from(P.music.map(o=>o)),s={},u=[];startMusicGame=()=>{score=0,u=[...x],getNewQuestion()};getNewQuestion=()=>{let o=["","","",""];const e=Math.floor(Math.random()*u.length);s=u[e],W.innerText=s.question;for(let i=0;i<s.options.length;i++)o[i]=s.options[i];b.nextSibling.textContent=o[0],M.nextSibling.textContent=o[1],C.nextSibling.textContent=o[2],S.nextSibling.textContent=o[3],u.splice(e,1)};startMusicGame();document.getElementById("coding");document.getElementById("music");document.getElementById("moderart");let A=document.getElementById("question");document.getElementsByClassName("choice-text");let k=document.getElementById("option1"),I=document.getElementById("option2"),E=document.getElementById("option3"),B=document.getElementById("option4");document.getElementById("nextQuestion");let G={music:[{id:1,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",options:["Standard notation","Tab notation","Morse code notation","Graphics notation"],answer:"Morse code notation",category:"music"},{id:2,question:"What is the most common time signature in classical music?",options:["3/4","4/4","5/4","6/8"],answer:"4/4",category:"music"},{id:3,question:"Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",options:["Violin","Piano","Harp","Theremin"],answer:"Theremin",category:"music"},{id:4,question:"What is the most common key in pop music?",options:["C Major","G Major","D Major","A Major"],answer:"C Major",category:"music"},{id:5,question:"Which of the following is not a type of chord?",options:["Major","Minor","Diminished","Flat"],answer:"Flat",category:"music"},{id:6,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",options:["Jazz","Blues","Rock","Applesauce"],answer:"Applesauce",category:"music"},{id:7,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",options:["Harmony","Counterpoint","Form","Cooking"],answer:"Cooking",category:"music"},{id:8,question:"What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",options:["Allegro","Andante","Adagio","Moderato"],answer:"Allegro",category:"music"},{id:9,question:"Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",options:["Sonata","Symphony","Concerto","Spaghetti"],answer:"Spaghetti",category:"music"},{id:10,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",options:["Sibelius","Finale","MuseScore","Microsoft Word"],answer:"Microsoft Word",category:"music"}],"modern-art":[{id:11,question:"Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:12,question:"Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Futurism","Cubism"],answer:"Cubism",category:"modern-art"},{id:13,question:"Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:14,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",options:["Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Edvard Munch","Claude Monet"],answer:"Edvard Munch",category:"modern-art"},{id:15,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Fauvism","Cubism"],answer:"Fauvism",category:"modern-art"},{id:16,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",options:["Impressionism","Futurism","Surrealism","Abstract Expressionism"],answer:"Futurism",category:"modern-art"},{id:17,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",options:["Claude Monet","Paul Cezanne","Paul Gauguin","Paul Klee"],answer:"Claude Monet",category:"modern-art"},{id:18,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",options:["Henri Matisse","Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Pablo Picasso"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:19,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",options:["Claude Mone","Paul Cezanne","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:20,question:"Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",options:["Auguste Rodin","Alexander Calder","Jean Arp","Henry Moore"],answer:"Auguste Rodin",category:"modern-art"}],coding:[{id:21,question:"What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",options:["if (condition):","if condition","if: condition","if condition:"],answer:"if condition:",category:"coding"},{id:22,question:"Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",options:["String","Number","Boolean","ArrayList"],answer:"ArrayList",category:"coding"},{id:23,question:"Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",options:["var","let","const","int"],answer:"int",category:"coding"},{id:24,question:"What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",options:["for i = 0 to 10","for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)","for (int i = 0; i <= 10)","for i in range(0, 10)"],answer:"for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",category:"coding"},{id:25,question:"Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",options:["while","for","do-while","foreach"],answer:"foreach",category:"coding"},{id:26,question:"Which of the following is not a valid operator in C++?",options:["+","-","*","$"],answer:"$",category:"coding"},{id:27,question:"In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"Python",category:"coding"},{id:28,question:"What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",options:["function name()","def name","function name","def name()"],answer:"def name()",category:"coding"},{id:29,question:"Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",options:["Int","String","Double","Object"],answer:"Object",category:"coding"},{id:30,question:"In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"C++",category:"coding"}]},F=Array.from(G["modern-art"].map(o=>o)),r={},d=[];startModernArtGame=()=>{score=0,d=[...F],getNewQuestion()};getNewQuestion=()=>{let o=["","","",""];const e=Math.floor(Math.random()*d.length);r=d[e],A.innerText=r.question.toString();for(let i=0;i<r.options.length;i++)o[i]=r.options[i];k.nextSibling.textContent=o[0],I.nextSibling.textContent=o[1],E.nextSibling.textContent=o[2],B.nextSibling.textContent=o[3],d.splice(e,1)};startModernArtGame();
